well what does make biblical counseling
那是什么使圣经辅导
biblical I'll tell you my friend
圣经我会告诉你我的朋友
biblical counseling is biblical because
圣经辅导是圣经的，因为
it relies on the Holy Spirit to enable
它依靠圣灵使
the change of putting to death the deeds
把行为变为死亡的行为
of the flesh
肉体
what makes biblical counseling biblical
是什么让圣经辅导圣经
biblical counseling is biblical because
圣经辅导是圣经的， 因为
the homework that we give our counsel
我们提供咨询的家庭作业
easy tweak is from the Word of God
容易调整来自神的话语
what makes biblical counseling biblical
是什么让圣经辅导圣经
when we're sitting across from a person
当我们坐在一个人的对面时
who's struggling with the issues of life
谁在努力解决生活问题
we're communicating the truth of God by
我们正在通过传达上帝的真理
exhorting and preaching the word with
劝诫和宣讲这个词
the authority it demands
它要求的权威
what makes biblical counseling biblical
是什么让圣经辅导圣经
it's based on and at theologically
它基于并在神学上
accurate Biblio a what makes biblical
准确的Biblio是什么使圣经
counseling biblical I'll tell you
咨询圣经我会告诉你
biblical counseling is biblical because
圣经辅导是圣经的，因为
the end result is God having changed a
最终结果是上帝改变了一个
human life through the power of his word
人生通过他的话语的力量
in his sufficient grace what makes
在他充分的恩典中是什么造成的
biblical counseling biblical biblical
圣经辅导圣经圣经
counseling is biblical because the
咨询是圣经， 因为
mission of the counselor is to emulate
辅导员的使命是效仿
the love of Jesus Christ in the
耶稣基督的爱
relationship with the counselee what
与辅导员的关系是什么
makes biblical counseling biblical I'll
我会做圣经辅导圣经
tell you my friend biblical counseling
告诉你我的朋友圣经辅导
is biblical because the end of a case
是圣经，因为一个案件​​的结束
where the counsel ease response to the
律师轻松回应
word is negative I don't believe that
字是消极的我不相信
I'm not going to do that is a warning
我不会这样做是警告
for the Christian it's a warning from
对于基督徒来说，这是一个警告
Hebrews 12 5 through 11 you're inviting
希伯来书12 5到11 你邀请
God's discipline my friend you were
上帝的纪律是你的朋友
asking God can you knock me down and the
问上帝你能打倒我吗？
answer to that question is yes and when
回答这个问题是肯定的，何时
he does it will hurt but he will do it
他这样做会伤害但他会这样做
because he loves you and somewhere amid
因为他爱你，在某个地方
the pain you'll come to your senses and
你会感觉到的痛苦
repent and you'll be walking with God
悔改，你将与上帝同行
for the unbeliever its Romans 1:18 232
为不信的人罗马书1:18232
it's the warning that one more time
这是另一次的警告
you've heard the truth of the gospel and
你听说过福音的真理，
you're turning away what makes biblical
你正在转向那些使圣经成为现实的东西
counseling biblical biblical counseling
咨询圣经的圣经辅导
is biblical because the purpose of the
是圣经，因为的目的
counselor and the purpose at the end for
辅导员和最后的目的
the counseling is to do all things to
心理咨询是做所有的事情
the glory of God
上帝的荣耀
what makes biblical counseling biblical
是什么让圣经辅导圣经
biblical counseling is biblical because
圣经辅导是圣经的，因为
it exalts the Word of God as the eternal
它高举神的话语作为 永恒
truth biblical counseling is biblical
真理圣经辅导是圣经的
because it exalts God as all-wise and
因为它以全智的方式高举上帝
all-powerful and his glory as the reason
无所不能和他的荣耀是理由
for living biblical counseling is
对于生活的圣经辅导是
biblical because in the cases with the
圣经， 因为在案件中
most severe human problems the answer is
最严重的人类问题的答案是
always the same what does the Bible say
总是和圣经所说的相同
about that biblical counseling is
关于那个圣经的辅导是
biblical because we believe that the
圣经， 因为我们相信
Bible is sufficient for every need of
圣经足以满足每一个需要
every believer so if your purpose is to
每一个信徒，所以如果你的目的是为了
offer accurate counsel from God's Word
从神的话语中提供准确的忠告
to the struggling people who come across
对遇到困难的人来说
your path in your life and biblical
你生活中的道路和圣经
counseling is what you're looking for
咨询是你正在寻找的
may God strengthen each of us to have a
愿上帝加强我们每个人的拥有
high view of his word as we consider our
在我们考虑我们的时候对他的话的高度看法
own lives our own circumstances our own
我们自己的生活我们自己的生活
choices and also as we provide answers
选择以及我们提供答案
to life questions for our counsel ease
为我们的建议轻松解决生活问题
and the people we disciple well we're
和我们门徒的人我们是
going to take a look at some other
去看看其他一些
answers to the question what makes
什么使得问题的答案
biblical counseling biblical during our
圣经辅导圣经在我们的期间
time that was my introduction let's take
这是我的介绍让我们采取的时间
a look at Roman numeral 2 what makes
看看罗马数字2是什么造成的
biblical counseling
圣经辅导
a theologically accurate Biblio lagea is
一个神学上准确的Biblio lagea是
its foundation point a the inspiration
它的基础点是灵感
and origin of the scriptures here is the
这里经文的起源是
truth
真相
second Timothy 3:16 and 17 all Scripture
提摩太后书3:16和17所有经文
is inspired by God and profitable for
是上帝和盈利为灵感
teaching for reproof for correction for
教导责备改正
training and righteousness that the man
这个男人的训练和正义
of God may be adequate equipped for
上帝可能已经足够了
every good work that identifies the
每一件能够识别出来的好作品
source of counsel that we need to give
我们需要提供的律师来源
ourselves and that we need to give to
我们自己和我们需要付出的
the people God brings across our path so
上帝带来的人如此
the words and ideas of Scripture
圣经的话语和思想
emanated from within the very being of
来自于内在的存在
God this elevates the Bible to a whole
上帝将圣经提升为一个整体
different level than than any other
不同于任何其他级别
source of potential truth the Scriptures
圣经潜在真理的来源
also also state the following 2nd Peter
还说明下面的第二个彼得
1 verses 1 of 20 and 21 there we go
我们去的是第 1 节20和21节
but know this first of all is that no
但要知道这首先是不
prophecy of Scripture is a matter of
圣经的预言是一个问题
one's own interpretation for no prophecy
一个人自己对没有预言的解释
was ever made by an act of human will
是有史以来 人类意志的行为作出
but men moved by the Holy Spirit spoke
但被圣灵感动的人说话了
from God
来自上帝
therefore the Word of God did not come
所以神的话语没有到来
from the will or the mind of man but
从人的意志或思想来看
from God himself
来自上帝自己
here are the applications in biblical
这里是圣经中的应用程序
counseling for these truths about the
为这些关于这些事实的真理提供咨询
inspiration and origin of the scriptures
经文的灵感和起源
since these things are true the word
因为这些东西都是真实的话
must be the final source of all counsel
必须是所有律师的最终来源
given to God's children no teachings of
赐给上帝的孩子没有教导
man can claim to originate from God in
人可以声称自己来自上帝
the same way and further because of
以同样的方式，并进一步因
their origins only the Scriptures can be
他们的起源只有圣经才可以
trusted and revered as true and as
信赖和尊敬为真实和尊重
authoritative because of these truths of
权威因为这些真理
Biblio lagea to say that biblical
Biblio lagea要说圣经
counseling is a counseling model that
咨询是一种咨询模式
uses the
使用
able to accomplish its purposes rather
能够完成其目的
it should be said that biblical
应该说，圣经
counseling determines its purposes by
咨询通过确定其目的
the content of God's Word in other words
换句话说，上帝之道的内容
the authority and biblical counseling is
权威和圣经辅导是
not what men write and think the essence
不是男人写的，而是思考本质
of biblical counseling is this
圣经辅导就是这个
communicating the Bible and
传达圣经和
theologically sound and accurate
神学上声音准确
applications of the Bible let's look at
我们应该看一下圣经的应用
point B in this section the authority of
B节在本节中的权威性
the scriptures here's the truth the
这里的经文是真实的
authority of the Bible is communicated
传达了圣经的权威
in many ways for most are the claims
在许多方面，对于大多数人来说是索赔
within the scriptures that they
在他们的经文中
originate from the Almighty God we
源于全能的上帝我们
looked at those in 2nd Timothy 3:16 and
看着提摩太后书3:16 和那些人
2nd Peter 1:20 and 21 also Jesus and the
彼得后书1:20和21也是耶稣和
New Testament writers regarded the Old
新约作家认为旧约
Testament as the Holy Word of God we see
遗嘱是我们所看到的神的圣言
that in the references in front of you
在你面前的参考文献中
similarly New Testament writers view
同样的新约作者观点
their own inspired writings and those of
他们自己的灵感着作和那些
each other as the Word of God as an
对方为神的话语作为
example 2nd Peter 3:16 of course also
例如， 彼得后书3:16当然也是
the accuracy and fulfillment of the
准确性和实现性
prophecies in the Bible also verify its
圣经中的预言也验证了它
authenticity so the truth of the
真实性所以真相
authority of the scriptures what are the
经文的权威是什么
applications of these important facts in
这些重要事实的应用
the biblical counseling room the Bible
圣经咨询室圣经
has ultimate authority over all matters
对所有事务拥有最终权力
it addresses Wayne Grudem in his
它解决了Wayne Grudem的问题
systematic theology accurately explains
系统神学准确地解释了
it this way quote the authority of
这种方式引用了权威
Scripture means that all the words in
圣经意味着所有的话语
scripture are God's words
经文是上帝的话
in such a way that to disbelieve or
以这样一种不相信或不相信的方式
disobey any word of Scripture is to
不服从圣经的任何一个词
disbelieve or disobey God end of quote
不相信或不服从上帝引用的结尾
the authority of God's Word makes it the
上帝之道的权威使它成为了
source for all good counsel since we can
我们可以为所有好律师提供资料
know the words of God the philosophy the
知道上帝哲学的话语
philosophies of man are rendered
人的哲学得以实现
inconsequential in the biblical
在圣经中无关紧要
counseling room the source of truth is
咨询室真相的来源是
Scripture the content of counsel is
经文是律师的内容
God's Word therefore the counselor must
因此，上帝的话语是辅导员必须的
proclaim God's Word with the authority
用权柄宣告上帝的话语
it demands Roman numeral 3 accurate
它要求罗马数字3准确
counsel from the Bible this is our part
圣经中的律师这是我们的一部分
this is the part that takes hard work
这是需要努力的部分
and good research and good data
和良好的研究和良好的数据
gathering with our counsel ease but what
我们的建议很容易收集， 但是什么
makes biblical counseling biblical is
使圣经辅导圣经是
when the counselor is communicating the
当辅导员正在沟通时
word in an accurate and pertinent way
以准确和相关的方式说出来
letter a under 0.3 obeying Scripture
写一封0.3以下的服从经文
determines the effects of adversity
决定逆境的影响
here's the truth Matthew 7 verses 24 to
这里的真相马太福音7节24
29 Jesus speaking he said quote
29 耶稣说他说的话
therefore everyone who hears these words
因此每个人都听到这些话
of mine and acts upon them may be
我和他们的行为可能是
compared to a wise man who built his
相对于一个聪明人谁建造了
house on the rock and the rain fell and
房子在岩石上，雨水落下
the floods came and the winds blew and
洪水来了，风吹来了
slammed against that house and yet it
猛烈撞击那所房子然而它
did not fall for it had been founded on
没有因为它已经成立而堕落
the rock everyone who hears these words
每个人听到这些话的摇滚乐
of mine and does not act upon them will
我的并不会对他们采取行动
be like a foolish man who built his
就像一个愚蠢的人建立他的
house on the sand the rains fell the
房子在沙滩上下雨了
floods came and the winds blew and
洪水来了， 风吹来了
slammed against that house and it fell
猛烈撞击那所房子，它倒下了
and great was its fall
它的陨落很棒
when Jesus had finished these words the
当耶稣完成这些话时
crowds were amazed at his teaching for
人们对他的教学感到惊讶
he was teaching them as one having
他正在教他们
authority not as their scribes what are
权威不像他们的抄写员那样
the applications of Matthew 7 24 to 29
马太福音724至29的申请
in biblical counseling first hard times
在圣经辅导的第一次艰难时期
reveal life's foundation this passage is
揭示这段经文的生命基础
so pertinent because so many people who
如此相关， 因为有这么多人
come to you and ask for help in biblical
来找你， 要求在圣经帮助
counseling are in the middle of the
咨询是在中间
storm they can relate to what Jesus was
风暴他们可以与耶稣是什么有关
talking about their life feels like it
谈论他们的生活感觉就像它
might feel in here if there was a
如果有的话可能会感觉到这里
torrential downpour and maybe
倾盆大雨也许
hurricane-force winds going on and maybe
飓风逼风，也许
a window or two blown out the rain is
一两个窗户被雨吹了
coming down we're in the middle of the
下来我们在 的 中间
storm what's going to happen and that's
风暴会发生什么，那就是
how life feels what's going to be the
生活是如何感受到的
outcome is the house still going to be
结果仍然是房子
standing or is it going to be
站立或是否会成为
obliterated by the rising waves outside
被外面升起的波浪所抹杀
hard times reveal life's foundation and
困难时期揭示了生活的基础和
a Christians response to the word
基督徒对这个词的回应
influence is greatly the impact of
影响力的影响很大
trials is that an understatement or what
试验是轻描淡写还是什么
because what Jesus tells us there is
因为耶稣告诉我们的是
there the differences of the two roads
两条路的差异
the two foundations the reaction to his
两个基金会对他的反应
word the person who hears it and acts
说出听到它并采取行动的人
upon it the house is still standing at
在它上面，房子仍然站着
the end it's as strong as it ever was
到底这是因为它以前一样强
it's not stronger but for the person
它并不强，但对于这个人
living in the house they're more
住在房子里他们更多
confident in the house aren't they so
自信的房子不是他们如此
there's there's the one option and the
有一个选项和
other one is and it's it's like those
另一个是，它就像那些
it's like the video that we see on the
这就像我们在看视频
11 o'clock news when you know some big
11点新闻当你知道一些大事
storm came in and the house is facing
风暴来了，房子正面临着
the wrong way in Malibu just got blitter
在马里布错误的方式刚刚得到了阻碍
rated by 14-foot waves so the response
按照14英尺波浪评定的反应
to the word for this person who's come
对于这个来的人来说
to you for help will determine whether
给你的帮助将决定是否
at the end of the storm they're standing
在风暴结束时他们站着
stronger and more confident than ever
比以往更强大，更自信
or the metaphorical house that is their
或者是他们的隐喻房子
life is obliterated many Christians over
生活被许多基督徒所摧毁
the years have sought counsel at Valley
多年来，他们一直在Valley寻求咨询
Bible Counseling Center at my church in
圣经咨询中心在我的教会
Lancaster and many of those people the
兰开斯特和很多人都是
reason they thought that help was they
因此，他们认为帮助是他们
were in the middle of the storm and they
是在暴风雨中，他们中间
they weren't sure what was going to
他们不知道发生了什么事情
happen and they were afraid they wanted
发生了， 他们害怕他们想要
help at the most severe time in their
帮助他们在最严峻的时间
life the troubles were significant all
生活中的麻烦都很重要
the different things sometimes a spouse
不同的事情有时是配偶
passed away unexpectedly somebody lost a
意外地去世了， 有人失去了一个
career type job school was different
职业类型的工作学校是不同的
difficult a traumatic failure upcoming
即将到来的创伤性失败很难
surgery no friends many others so a
手术没有朋友很多人这么一个
biblical counselor when when you're
当你的时候，圣经辅导员
meeting with people at those times in
在那个时候与人们会面
life what do you tell them do your part
生活你告诉他们你做了什么
to study the word diligently and to
勤奋学习这个词
gather good information so that you can
收集好的信息，以便你可以
communicate accurately the truth of God
准确地传达上帝的真理
word God's Word as it applies to them in
说出上帝的话语，因为它适用于他们
their circumstances that day one of my
他们的情况那天我的一个
counselors had lost a significant job
辅导员失去了一份重要的工作
months went by and he had to start over
几个月过去了，他不得不重新开始
in a different field of work so
在不同的工作领域如此
entry-level much less pay he was in the
入门级的要少得多的薪酬，他在
middle of the storm he didn't know how
他不知道怎么回事
to handle it he didn't know how it was
来处理它，他不知道是怎么回事
going to turn out and so that's why he
结果，所以这就是他的原因
picked up the phone and called the
拿起电话打来电话
church office and said I need to talk to
教会办公室，说我需要跟
someone well Matthew 7:24 229 provided
有人也太7:24229提供
vital truth for him he had a choice and
对他来说至关重要的事实是他有选择权
that choice involved how he would
那个选择涉及他的意愿
respond to God's Word God was very
回应上帝的话语上帝是非常的
interested in what choice he made in
感兴趣的他做出什么样的选择
that particular case the core of it all
这个特殊情况就是它的核心
was Matthew 6:25 234
是马太福音6:25 234
and it had two significant implications
它有两个重要的含义
in that passage Jesus taught to not be
在耶稣所教导的那段经文中
anxious over life on earth and he said
对地球上的生命感到焦虑，他说
to seek first his kingdom and his
首先寻求他的王国和他的王国
righteousness with this particular man
与这个特殊的人正义
we'll call him Chris he had often viewed
我们会称他为经常看过的克里斯
his success in the business place and
他在商业上的成功和
his wealth as completely his own doing
他的财富完全是他自己所做的
and so one of his biggest fears was he
所以他最大的恐惧之一就是他
was going to lose a lot of this stuff
会失去很多这样的东西
that he had accumulated also in that
他也积累了那个
career that ended he did not work as a
事业结束了他没有工作作为一个
man seeking God's righteousness rather
相反，人寻求上帝的正义
he competed with coworkers and he did
他与同事竞争，他做到了
whatever he needed to do to surpass them
无论他需要做什么来超越他们
so for Chris acting upon Jesus words in
因此，克里斯在耶稣的话语中行事
Matthew 6 we required acknowledging
马太福音6章我们要求承认
God's sovereignty and not worrying about
上帝的主权而不是担心
the things that he might lose it also
他也可能失去它的东西
required him to be thankful to do the
要求他感谢做到这一点
good humble work of an entry-level guy
一个入门级家伙的良好谦逊工作
for the purpose of bringing glory and
为了带来荣耀和
honor to God as opposed to competing
尊重上帝，而不是竞争
with all these other people so that he
与所有这些其他人一起让他
can get promoted sooner the choices he
可以尽快得到提升他的选择
would make would have huge consequences
会产生巨大的后果
because he was in the middle of the
因为他在中间
storm he heard the words of Christ was
风暴他听到了基督的话
he going to act upon them and have the
他会采取行动并拥有他们
outcome of the storm be his house
风暴的结局是他的房子
standing his life still standing or was
站在他的生活仍然站立或是
he going to not act upon the words of
他不会采取行动的话
Christ want the things he had wanted
基督想要他想要的东西
live the way he had lived worked the way
住他生活的方式的工作方式
he had worked and his house would be
他工作过，他的房子是
obliterated by this storm that was
被这场风暴所掩盖
really the choice all of that was
真的是所有这一切的选择
hanging in the balance
悬在天平
well fortunately Chris repented of his
幸运的是克里斯忏悔了他的
sins and he did replace anxiety with
罪过他确实取代了焦虑
honoring God he got to the point where
尊重上帝， 他到了那里
he chose to work for God's glory alone
他选择独自为上帝的荣耀而工作
and he was willing to accept whatever
他愿意接受任何东西
accumulation of wealth and things fell
财富和事物的积累下降了
by the wayside so as he was this humble
在路边， 所以他是这个谦虚
man doing his work for the sake of God's
男人在做他的工作，为 上帝的缘故
glory making less than half of what he
荣耀不到他的一半
used to in this entry-level position in
曾经在这个入门级的位置
the new field he would review Matthew 7
他将审查马修7的新领域
24 to 29 every day and he was comforted
每天24到29岁，他得到了安慰
because no matter the severity or the
因为无论严重程度如何
duration of his tribulation at the end
最后他的苦难的持续时间
he would be standing and he would be
他会站着，他会
standing with God and standing on the
站在上帝的立场上
promises in truth of God's Word that was
真实地承诺上帝的话语
exciting and that's what happened that's
令人兴奋，这就是发生的事情
how it turned out for Chris his
它是如何横空出世 ，他的克里斯
adventure and the ultimate obedience to
冒险和最终的服从
Matthew 7:24 229 demonstrate the
马太福音7:24 229证明了
sufficiency of God's Word for a person
上帝 对一个人 的话语的充分性
who's suffering through adversity well
谁在逆境中受苦很好
Roman numeral three letter B another
罗马数字三字母B另一个
important truth about the Scriptures is
关于圣经的重要事实是
this the Bible's unique incision into
这是圣经中独特的切口
the soul here's the truth
这里的灵魂是真理
consider Hebrews four 12 and 13 for the
考虑希伯来书4个12和13的
word of God is active and sharper than
神的话是积极和更清晰的比
any two-edged sword and piercing as far
任何双刃剑和穿孔到目前为止
as the division of soul and spirit of
作为灵魂和精神的分裂
both joints and marrow and able to judge
关节和骨髓都能判断
the thoughts and intentions of the heart
心灵的想法和意图
and there is no creature hidden from his
并且没有任何生物隐藏在他的身上
sight but all things are open and laid
视线， 但所有的东西都是敞开的
bare to the eyes of him with whom we
我和他们一同睁不开眼睛
have
有
do powerful passage application and
做强大的通道申请和
biblical counseling the Word of God is
圣经辅导上帝的话语是
able to judge the thoughts and
能够判断和思考
intentions of the heart that tells us
心灵的意图告诉我们
that this one thing the Word of God is
这一件事是上帝的话语
his instrument to judge the hearts of
他用来判断心中的工具
men
男人
we know from Proverbs that God critiques
我们从箴言中知道上帝的批评
our purposes in proverbs 16 2 it says
我们在谚语中的目的162它说
the Lord weighs the motives and in
主在权衡动机和权利
proverbs 17 2 it says the Lord tests
箴言17 2它说主测验
hearts so we see the role of the word in
所以我们看到了这个词的作用
this process in Hebrews 4 12 and 13 the
这个过程在希伯来书4章12和13章中
word exposes the thoughts and intentions
这个词揭示了思想和意图
of the heart well only God can fully
心里只有上帝才能完全
know hearts I think that often people
知道我认为经常是人
don't even realize their own purposes
甚至没有意识到自己的目的
clearly but God certainly does he knows
显然，但上帝肯定知道
exactly why you and I do each thing that
究竟为什么你和我做每一件事
we do but in a biblical counseling case
我们在圣经咨询案例中这样做
where our purpose is inner person change
我们的目的是内心的变化
where the end game is a heart that is
结束游戏的核心是什么
driven by obedience to God interaction
顺从上帝互动的驱使
at the heart level is absolutely vital
在心脏层面是绝对重要的
if we can facilitate our counsel ly
如果我们能够方便我们的律师LY
interfacing with God's Word at the
在神的话语中与神的话语接触
deepest level of the soul God will
上帝将最深层次的灵魂
expose the counsel Lee's motives it's a
揭露律师李的动机是一个
fact how can it not be the Hebrews 4 12
事实上， 它怎么也不能希伯来人4月12日
and 13 tells us that and God will
13告诉我们，上帝会
communicate he will reveal to the
沟通他会透露给
counsel Lee his judgment of the desires
律师Lee对欲望的判断
that he's finding in the heart if the
他在心里找到了
counsel Lee is willing to talk about
律师李愿意谈谈
that encounter with God or write about
与神或写那次偶遇
that encounter with God then we will be
与神那次偶遇，然后我们会
able to counsel from the Scriptures most
能够从圣经中最律师
effectively because we'll understand
因为我们会理解
those thoughts and intentions the
那些想法和意图
motives
动机
of the heart that God has revealed to
上帝启示的心脏
his child
他的孩子
so God exposes and judges the believers
所以上帝揭露并审判信徒
heart that's what it says in Hebrews 4
这就是它在希伯来书4中所说的内容
12 and 13 look at the description of
参见图12和13的描述
God's exposing and judging the believers
上帝揭露并判断信徒
heart in verse 13 the NASB reads all
在第13节的心脏，NASB读取所有
things are open and laid bare to the
事情是敞开的，露出来的
eyes of him with whom we have to do the
与我们有关的他的眼睛
ESV says all are naked and exposed to
ESV说所有人都赤裸裸地接触过
the eyes of him to whom we must give
我们必须给予他的眼睛
account the latter is really more
帐户后者真的更多
literal there's a sense of authority in
文字中有一种权威感
the Greek words and the literal words
希腊词和字面词
are naked and grabbed by the throat
赤身裸体，被喉咙抓住
somebody pictured that okay well
有人想象得那么好
linguists who study the word say that
研究这个词的语言学家说
this may be a reference to a wrestling
这可能是对摔跤的参考
move that leaves the person limp and
让人跛行的举动
powerless or some position where the
无力或某些位置
person is completely subdued and they
人完全被制服了他们
can't get free so when you think about
当你想到的时候，就无法获得自由
the culture of the Roman world to whom
罗马世界的文化对谁
this is written most police officers in
这是大多数警察写的
those cities were retired veterans of
那些城市是退休的退伍军人
war and they were regarded as heroes
战争，他们被视为英雄
kind of like retired veterans of war in
有点像退役的退伍军人
this country say in the 1940s so we have
这个国家在二十世纪四十年代说我们有
this picture of what happens when God
这张上帝发生的事情
exposes the motives of the heart it's
暴露心脏的 动机 是
like the the six for 240 pound police
就像六英镑的240英镑警察一样
officer engages you in a public place
官员让你在一个公共场所
he's tackled you down and he's got you
他解决了你，他找到了你
in this position where you you can't
在这个位置，你不能
move and perhaps you have one of those
移动，也许你有其中一个
dress like things and it's like not
穿得像事情，就像没有
covering everything - based on that
涵盖一切- 基于此
other word
换句话说
so it's humiliating and you're
所以这是令人羞辱的，你是
completely helpless
完全无助
this guy's knee is in your chest and
这家伙的膝盖是在你的胸部和
you're gasping for air and you can't
你大口喘气，你不能
move your arms or your legs
移动你的手臂或腿
it's quite a graphic image if you and I
如果你和我，这是一个非常形象的图像
are paying attention every day when we
我们每天都在关注
spend our time in the word we know what
花时间在单词我们知道什么
this is like God exposes the thoughts
这就像上帝暴露了思想
and intentions of our heart and that
我们内心的意图和那种意图
gives us a choice what do we do then
我们可以选择我们做什么
do we repent of sins that are exposed do
我们悔改暴露的罪吗？
we give thanks for the good things that
我们在感谢的好东西，
he's showing us that exist in our
他向我们展示了存在于我们身上的东西
motives do we seek his help through His
动机我们是否通过他的帮助寻求他的帮助
grace and through the word to replace
恩惠并通过这个词来取代
those sins with righteousness
那些有正义的罪
those are humbling times the times that
这些都是震撼人心倍倍
God exposes that thoughts and intentions
上帝暴露了这种想法和意图
of my heart and there's evil involved
我的心脏和邪恶参与其中
there I I hate myself then it's it's
我讨厌自己然后就是这样
difficult personally I think that if God
个人很难我认为如果上帝
revealed everything evil that he saw in
揭露了他所看到的一切邪恶
me all at once I think I would die I
我一下子就认为我会死的
think that would be too much at once but
认为那会是太多了但是
God sovereignly because of his holiness
由于他的圣洁，上帝是主权的
and because of his love when we're
因为他的爱，当我们
paying attention in our time in the word
在我们的时间里关注这个词
he reveals some of it and he gives us
他揭示了一些， 他给了我们
this opportunity there we are helpless
这个机会我们很无奈
like the guard with his knee in our
像我的膝盖护膝一样
chest and we can't move but what do we
胸部，我们不能动，但我们做什么
do what do we do
做我们做什么
if we repent of our sin and if we seek
如果我们悔改我们的罪，如果我们寻求
his sufficient grace to be doers of the
他足够优雅地成为了他们的行动者
word then there's a great result of that
那么这就是一个很好的结果
somewhere down the road as he enables us
因为他使我们能够在路上的某个地方
to put to death those deeds of the flesh
将那些肉体的行为处死
that are so humiliating at that moment
那一刻真是太羞辱了
we need those times with the Lord
我们需要与主同一时间
they're painful at the moment but
他们现在很痛苦但是
they're beautiful in the end how could
他们到底是多么美丽
we live without them we realize who God
我们没有他们， 我们认识到谁是上帝
is and who we are and we see the purpose
我们是谁，我们是谁，我们看到了目的
of life very clearly lord I will subject
生活非常清楚领主我会受到影响
my will to yours Lord I repent of this
我对你的意志主我悔改了
sin or I will strive to obey your word
罪或我会努力服从你的话
father will you strengthen me to be a
父亲，你会加强我成为一个
doer of the word in this area of my life
在我生命的这个方面，这个词的实践者
our counsel leaves need these times with
我们的律师需要这些时间
God as well because these interactions
上帝也是因为这些互动
with God are the core of change on the
与神的变化对核心
top of page 101 there's a question how
在页面101的顶部有一个问题如何
can we use the scriptures to give our
我们可以用经文给我们的
counsel ease the best opportunities to
律师安慰最好的机会
have these kinds of meetings with God
与上帝有这些会面
there's a vital component to
这是至关重要的组成部分
discipleship for biblical counseling
圣经辅导的门徒训练
here because if we can somehow if we can
在这里，因为如果我们可以，我们可以
somehow facilitate this kind of
在某种程度上有利于这种
interaction between our counsel II and
我们的律师和II之间的互动
the Lord then true change can occur and
然后主可以发生真正的改变
if what goes on there is submission to
如果发生了什么事情就会提交给
God's Word and the commitment to obeying
上帝的话语和服从的承诺
him the result will be great no storm
他的结果将是伟大的没有风暴
can touch your counsel II if that's the
可以触摸你的律师II，如果那是
result so here are some answers for
结果所以这里有一些答案
consideration how can we use the
考虑我们如何使用
scriptures to give our counsel ease the
经文让我们的建议轻松自如
best opportunity to have these meetings
举行这些会议的最佳机会
with God 1 the scriptures must be the
与上帝1经文必须是
focal point of your biblical counseling
圣经辅导的焦点
me telling people like how my mom did
我告诉人们我的妈妈是怎么做的
things isn't going to help them
事情不会对他们有所帮助
my mom was a nice lady okay come on they
我妈妈是个好女人，好吧来吧
really know that's not going to help all
真的知道这不会对所有人有所帮助
right number two when you prepare to
当你准备好时，正确的第二个
teach a strategic passage from God's
教导上帝的战略段落
Word for an upcoming counseling session
即将到来的咨询会议的话
here's a suggestion carefully composed
这是一个精心编写的建议
to precise questions that will force
精确的问题，将迫使
your counsel ly to consider the passage
你的律师会考虑这段经文
at the heart level with God God will be
与上帝在心灵层面上帝会成为
doing his part you can be sure they
尽他所能，你可以肯定他们
might ignore him but he will be judging
可能会忽视他，但他会评判
the thoughts and intentions of the heart
心灵的想法和意图
then carefully word a third question to
然后仔细说出第三个问题
ask the counsel II to share the results
请律师II分享结果
of God's exposing of his heart he can
他能够揭露他的内心
choose not to answer that question but
选择不回答这个问题但是
if he does then you have a great
如果他这样做那么你就会很棒
opportunity a great opportunity to
机会是一个很好的机会
counsel from the Scriptures at the
在从圣经律师
deepest level of the soul number three
最深层次的灵魂三号
craft homework that forces your counsel
制作强制你的建议的作业
to consider the scriptures that address
考虑经文该地址
his area of sin at the inner person
他内心深处的罪恶领域
level and then ask him to write about it
水平，然后让他写下来
for convince your counsel Lee that your
说服你的律师李你的
purposes are God's glory and your
目的是上帝的荣耀和你的
counsel leaves benefit I think that's an
律师离开福利我认为这是一个
important aspect of trust in this
信任的重要方面
relationship five convince your counsel
关系五说服你的忠告
Lee that you love him with a christ-like
李，你爱他与基督一样
love and number six be patient your part
爱和第六是耐心的你的一部分
in all of this what's going on between
在所有这一切是怎么回事之间
this soul of your counsel Lee or your
这个你的律师李或你的灵魂
disciple II and the Lord your part in
弟子二和耶和华你的角色
all of it is a careful interaction with
所有这一切都是与之密切互动的
God and with that person but what a
上帝和那个人，但是什么
privilege to be involved in such a
参与这样一个特权的特权
ministry and what a joy it is when you
部和什么是快乐是当你
see God doing what you know he will
看到上帝按你所知的去做
and then that Christian brother or
然后那个基督徒兄弟或者
sister responding and then change occurs
姐姐回应然后发生变化
and it's changed that the starts at that
它开始就改变了
core level as their knee was talking
他们的膝盖正在谈论的核心水平
about in the last hour
在最后一小时
wow what a joy Roman numeral three
哇多么喜欢罗马数字三
points see God's generous provisions in
要点看上帝慷慨的规定
regard to his use of the word
关于他对这个词的使用
this passage of great hope and loving
这段充满希望和爱的经历
provision is the powerful conclusion for
条款是有力的结论
the person whose heart was exposed in
心脏暴露的人
Hebrews 4 12 and 13 and who responded by
希伯来书4 12和13，并作出回应
repenting of sin here it is
在这里忏悔罪
a few verses later Hebrews 4:15 and 16
几节后希伯来书4:15和16节
for we do not have a high priest who
因为我们没有一个大祭司
cannot sympathize with our weaknesses
不能同情我们的弱点
but one who has been tempted in all
但是一个受过诱惑的人
things as we are yet without sin
因为我们还没有犯罪
therefore let us draw near with
因此，让我们靠近
confidence to the throne of grace so
信心的恩典的宝座等等
that we may receive mercy and find grace
我们可以得到怜悯并找到恩典
to help in time of need
在需要时提供帮助
here are the applications in biblical
这里是圣经中的应用程序
counseling if after God has exposed my
如果在上帝暴露我的情况后提供咨询
motives and my sins by the active use of
动机和我的罪恶积极使用
his word if at that point my desire is
他的话，如果那时我的愿望是
to replace sin with righteousness then
那么用正义取代罪
this passage Hebrews 4:15 and 16 is a
这段经文希伯来书4:15和16是一个
cause for rejoicing look what it says it
欣喜的原因看看它说的是什么
says that Jesus Christ my Lord
说耶稣基督是我的主
understands he's been tempted in every
明白他每个人都受到诱惑
way just like me yet without sin since
就像我一样没有犯罪的方式
he is in me and I am in him since the
他在我 身边，从那以后我就在他身边
theology of the union with Christ is
与基督联合的神学是
true the Scriptures teach that this
这是圣经所教导的
union with Christ he is in me and I am
与基督联合，他是在我和 我
in him that tells me that this sin can
他告诉我这罪可以
be overcome regardless of its frequency
无论频率如何，都要克服
or its severity that is that is powerful
或其严重性是强大的
hope we have that our counsel ease must
我们希望我们的律师能够轻松自如
have that and then in verse 16 God is
有这个然后在第16节上帝是
telling me to confidently ask for the
告诉我自信地要求
two things that I really need at that
我真正需要的两件事
point his grace and His mercy His grace
指出他的恩典和怜悯他的恩典
which is really a synonym for help is
这是真正需要帮助的同义词是
exactly what I need if I'm going to keep
正如我要保留的那样，正是我所需要的
the door close to this sin and not go
门接近这个罪而不去
back to it again I need his help and
再回到它我需要他的帮助和
he's telling me to ask confidently for
他告诉我要自信地问
that help
这种帮助
now how kind is the Lord and I also need
现在主和我也需要 多么善良
his mercy as a Christian I was not in
他作为基督徒的怜悯我不在
danger of losing my salvation but as a
失去救恩的危险，但作为一个
Christian I was inviting God's
克里斯蒂安一世正在邀请上帝
discipline with my sin of frequency or
用我的频率或罪恶来训练
severity but now I've repented I've
严重程度，但现在我后悔我已经
intentionally purposed to not sin in
故意故意不犯罪
this way again I've turned from pursuing
这种方式我再次转向追求
that sin to pursuing obeying the word
追求顺从这个词的罪
and so I can be assured that I'm
所以我可以放心，我
restored to him completely and therefore
完全恢复了他，因此
I am not in danger of discipline how
我没有纪律的危险
kind is the Lord so if your counsel Lee
如果你的律师李，那就是主
is interacting with God in His Word at
在他的话语中与上帝互动
the level described in Hebrews 4:12 and
希伯来书4:12和
13 he needs to know the great hope of
13他需要知道的巨大希望
Hebrews 4:15 and 16 and so our part is
希伯来书4:15和16所以我们的部分是
communicate those things clearly
清楚地传达这些事情
what makes biblical counseling biblical
是什么让圣经辅导圣经
well Roman numeral 4 on page 102
第102页的罗马数字4
gives us another topic the Bible's
给了我们圣经的另一个主题
teaching on relationships is the
关系教学就是这样
counselors code of conduct the quote
辅导员的行为准则报价
that you have is from a book called
你必须从一本名为
counseling by John MacArthur and one of
John MacArthur和其中一位提供咨询
the chapters that Wayne Mack wrote is
Wayne Mack写的章节是
called developing a helping relationship
叫做发展帮助关系
with counsel ease and so he gives us a
律师轻松，所以他给了我们一个
ten point synopsis of how to demonstrate
十点简介如何演示
genuine compassion for your counsel ease
真诚地同情你的忠告
Wayne Mac is was a longtime board member
Wayne Mac是一位长期董事会成员
of the National Association of new feted
全国 新的受欢迎 协会
counselors he's now an Academy member he
辅导员他现在是学院的成员
lives in South Africa where he has a
他住在南非，在那里他有一个
flourishing ministry of biblical
繁荣的圣经事工
counseling and pastoral training and one
咨询和牧师培训和一个
of his frequent topics that he taught
他教过的频繁话题
about and wrote about was this kind of
约，并写下了这样的
relationship between the counselor and
辅导员与辅导员之间的关系
the counselor so here here the 10 points
辅导员所以这里这里的10分
he lists with the scriptures that he
他的经典，他列出
lists in that book
那本书中的清单
Philippians 1:8 tell your counsel II you
腓立比书1：8告诉你的律师我
for them Colossians 4 12 and 13 pray for
为他们西4 12和13祈祷
them and with them Romans 12:15 rejoice
他们和他们一同罗马书12:15欢喜快乐
with them and grieve with them Matthew
和他们在一起并为他们悲伤马修
12:20 with them gently and tenderly
12:20温柔而温柔地抚摸着他们
proverbs 15 23 be tactful or timely with
谚语15 23要巧妙或及时
your words Colossians 4:6 speak to them
你的话歌罗西书4：6对他们说话
with grace mark 1021 love and accept
以优雅标记1021爱和接受
them even when they have rejected your
他们甚至在拒绝你的时候
counsel that's an interesting way take a
律师这是一个有趣的方式
look at mark 10 21 Matthew 12 1 through
看马克10 21马修12 1到
7 defend them against those who mistreat
7保护他们免受那些虐待的人
and accuse them
并指责他们
that's real care Matthew 18 21 and 22
这是真正关心的马太福音18 21和22
forgive them of any wrong they have done
原谅他们任何错误，他们已经做的
to you and first John 3:17
对你和约翰一书3:17
if you are able and there is need meet
如果你能够并且需要见面
their physical needs it is a privilege
他们的身体需求是一种特权
for us as biblical counselors to serve
为我们服务的圣经辅导员
our fellow Christians by striving to
我们的基督徒同胞努力奋斗
emulate Christ's love
仿效基督的爱
what makes biblical counseling biblical
是什么让圣经辅导圣经
Roman numeral 5 middle of page 102 on
第102页中间的 罗马数字5
your conference notes in this section
您在本节中的会议记录
some of the words that I say are found
我说的一些话被发现了
in your notes and some are not but I am
在你的笔记中，有些不是，但我
going to go in order so I hope you can
要按顺序排进，所以我希望你能
stick with the same general flow that
坚持同样的一般流程
I'm going with in this section we're
我在本节我们用去
gonna examine other essential truths of
要研究其他基本事实
Biblio Legere the first of these
文献记录莱格尔这些第一
essentials essential truths is the
要点必不可少的事实是
Bible's Authority in regard to
关于圣经的权威
theological controversies the truth is
神学争论的真相是
John 17:17 God's Word is truth and Psalm
约翰福音17:17神的话语是真理和诗篇
1 1989 his word is also eternal forever
1989年他的话永远永恒
o Lord your word is settled in heaven
噢，你的话在天上定居
so the application in biblical
所以在圣经中的应用
counseling what what theological
辅导什么什么神学
controversies are there in our world
我们的世界有争议
today in our Christian culture there are
今天在我们的基督教文化中有
really two categories some theological
真的有两类神学
controversies are debates over doctrines
争论是关于学说的争论
of the Bible between Christians and
基督徒与圣经之间的圣经
unbelievers there are lots of these
不信的人有很多这些
because there are lots of churches that
因为有很多教堂
don't teach the gospel so these debates
所以这些辩论都不要教导福音
include distortions of the gospel and
包括福音的歪曲和
other misrepresentations of the Bible by
其他对圣经的歪曲
cults and by false religions in regard
邪教和虚假宗教
to these theological controversies we
对于这些神学上的争议我们
must stand for the truth of the word the
必须代表这个词的真相
authority of the scriptures and the
经文 和权威
integrity of the gospel in our time we
在我们这个时代福音的完整性，我们
must appeal to the clear truths of the
必须诉诸于明确的事实
word to oppose any heretical use of the
反对任何异端使用的词
Bible there's another kind of
圣经还有另一种
theological controversy that we run into
我们碰到 的神学争论
in our time and that is differing views
在我们这个时代，这是不同的观点
held by Christians who each use the
每个人都使用的基督徒持有
Bible as their authority so some
圣经作为他们的权威所以有些
examples from this category are
这个类别的例子是
different beliefs about end times events
关于结束时间事件的不同信念
or the value of affiliating with the
或者与之相关的价值
denomination or not for the local church
是否适用于当地教会
regarding theological controversies
关于神学争议
among ourselves or between us and other
我们之间或我们与其他人之间
true Christians such as the examples
真实的基督徒，如例子
just named we each should respectfully
刚刚命名我们每个人都应该尊重
present our own reasoning from the
从中提出我们自己的推理
Scriptures and listen with respect to
经文和倾听
the other side and then we each should
另一方然后我们每个人都应该
decide what we believe is true from
决定我们认为是真实的
God's Word and how the word applies to
上帝的话语以及这个词如何适用
that issue in our own life in church
在我们自己的教会生活中的这个问题
there's another area of this general
这个将军的另一个领域
category and that is general revelation
类别，这是普遍的启示
verses special revelation that's at the
经文特殊启示这是在
top of page 1 of
第1页的
the doctrine of general revelation as
作为一般启示的学说
unfolded in Scripture shows that God
在圣经中展开表明上帝
uses creation and the conscience of man
用创造和人的良心
to disclose particular facts about
披露有关具体事实
himself let's think this one through
我自己让我们想一想
Romans 1 19 to 21 says this quote
罗马书1-19至21说这句话
because that which is known about God is
因为那里面有人知道上帝是
evident within them for God made it
在他们里面 显而易见的 是上帝造就了
evident to them for since the creation
自创作以来对他们来说很明显
of the world his invisible attributes
世界上他看不见的属性
his eternal power and divine nature have
他永恒的力量和神圣的本性
been clearly seen being understood
已被清楚地看到被理解
through what has been made so that they
通过他们所做的一切
are without excuse for even though they
即使他们也没有任何借口
knew God they did not honor him as God
他们认识上帝，不尊重他为上帝
or give thanks but they became futile in
或者感谢，但他们变得徒劳无功了
their speculations and their foolish
他们的猜测和他们的愚蠢
heart was darkened so there's a biblical
心脏变暗所以有一个圣经
definition of general revelation and the
一般启示的定义和
purposes for it the applications in
目的为它的应用
biblical counseling every person who
圣经辅导每个人
ever lived has understood enough about
永远的生活已经足够了解
God that they could make choices about
上帝， 他们可以做出选择
honoring him or not we just read that
是否尊重他我们只是阅读
scripture also teaches the God
经文也教导上帝
disseminates truth of general general
传播将军的真相
revelation to man through nature Psalm
通过自然诗篇启示人类
19:1 through 6 and through the
19：1到6并通过
conscience Romans 2 14 and 15 so whether
良心罗马人2 14和15所以是否
whether people acknowledge it or not
人们是否承认与否
everyone knows or has known the facts
每个人都知道或了解事实
about God that he is disclosed through
关于上帝， 他是透露出来的
general revelation why is that important
一般的启示为什么那么重要
because general revelation is described
因为描述了一般的启示
in the scripture with a particular
在经文中有一个特别的
purpose it's something that's common to
目的是它的共同点
every person and the purpose is for
每个人和目的都是为了
giving people the opportunity to seek
给人们寻求机会
God and it holds them accountable if
如果，上帝和它让他们负责
they do not seek God that's what it says
他们并没有寻求上帝的意思
in Romans 1 19 and 20
在罗马书1章19和20节
ironically in our time some people use
讽刺的是在我们这个时代一些人使用
that term general revelation
那个词一般的启示
as a justification for using a source
作为使用来源的理由
other than the Scriptures as truth for
除了圣经之外的真理
counseling people struggling with life
建议人们在生活中挣扎
issues people who proposed to take
发布提议的人
truths from the Bible and truths from
圣经中的真理和来自的真理
all of these secular counselors in the
所有这些世俗的辅导员都在
last hundred and fifty years say that
过去一百五十年这么说
that is general revelation that is God
这是普遍的启示，就是上帝
revealing truth just like he revealed
揭露真相就像他透露的那样
truth in the Bible and so we could use
圣经中的真理， 所以我们可以使用
both of those to counsel people that's
这两个人都是为那些人提供咨询
different because when an when a
不同，因为什么时候一个
professing unbeliever comes up with a
自称不信的人想出了一个
counseling system and they're telling
咨询系统，他们正在讲述
you to use this in counseling people at
你 在辅导人用这个
the crossroads of life but it is not in
人生的十字路口，但它不是在
conformity with what the Bible is saying
符合圣经所说的
about that that's neither the identity
关于那不是身份
of general revelation nor is it the
一般的启示也不是
purpose of general revelation the
一般启示的目的
purpose of general revelation is to
一般启示的目的是
convict people of sin and to reveal
使罪人定罪并揭露
enough truth through creation and
足够的真相通过创造和
through their conscience that they could
通过他们的良心，他们可以
seek God there's also special revelation
寻求上帝也有特别的启示
special revelation occurs only through
特殊的启示只能通过
the Bible the essence of special
圣经是特殊的本质
revelation is its focus on the purpose
启示是它关注的目的
and propitiatory work of Jesus Christ
和耶稣基督的赎罪工作
through special revelation that is to
通过特殊启示来实现
say by God's Word every elected person
用上帝的话说每个当选的人
in the church age comes to salvation
在教会时代来到拯救
according to first Peter 1:22 2:25
根据彼得前书1:22 2:25
special revelation is also God's chosen
特别的启示也是上帝的选择
vehicle for the progressive
进步的车辆
sanctification of Scripture I mean of
我所指的圣经成圣
Christians excuse me so understanding
基督徒请原谅我这么理解
that the Bible is God's means for
圣经是上帝的手段
revealing truth in our time is also an
在我们这个时代揭示真相也是一个
important foundation of biblical
圣经的重要基础
counseling so I bring these these two
咨询所以我带这两个
points of theology for your
你的神学要点
consideration because you'll probably
考虑因为你可能会
hear them used in
听他们用过
different ways than then how the
不同的方式比如何
scriptures reveal the truth about the
经文揭示 了真相
topics they encompass so Roman numeral
它们包含的主题如此罗马数字
six our conclusion what makes biblical
六，我们的结论是什么使圣经成为现实
counseling biblical I'll tell you
咨询圣经我会告诉你
biblical counseling is biblical because
圣经辅导是圣经的，因为
its purpose is to honor and glorify God
它的目的是荣耀和荣耀上帝
by accurately following the truths of
通过准确地遵循真理
God's eternal Word and only those truths
上帝永恒的话语，只有那些真理
in every aspect of the counseling
在咨询的每个方面
process including but not limited to the
过程包括但不限于
purpose of counseling our view of God
咨询我们对上帝的看法的目的
our view of man our analysis of the
我们的人我们的分析观点
problem our source of counsel our source
问题我们的律师来源
of truth the definition of the solution
事实上解决方案的定义
the means of change the guide for
改变指南的方法
communication and the guide for
沟通和指南
relationships within the counseling
在辅导中关系
ministry the Word of God is adequate for
神的话语就足够了
each of these things God tells us that
上帝告诉我们的每一件事
his word is his instrument to equip us
他的话是他装备我们的工具
in each of these things in our own lives
在我们自己的生活中的每一件事
and in our ministry to others may God
在我们对别人的事工中，可能是上帝
strengthen each of us to counsel
加强我们每个人的建议
accurately from his word in discipleship
准确地从他在门徒训练中的话语
relationships in informal counseling
非正式咨询中的关系
conversations and in the formal
对话和正式的
counseling setting
咨询设置